Guide to the Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 1927-1974
Ross, Philip Collection of NLRB Documents
- 10-CA-4295; International Shoe Company, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 31)
- 10-CA-4296; Jocie-New Dixie Motor Lines, Inc., 1959 (Box 72, Folder 32)
- 10-CA-4297; Atlanta Newspapers, Inc., 1959 (Box 72, Folder 33)
- 10-CA-4298; American-Marietta Company, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 34)
- 10-CA-4316; Preferred Homes, Inc., 1959 (Box 72, Folder 35)
- 10-CA-4315; King Stove and Range co., 1959 (Box 72, Folder 36)
- 10-CA-4314; E. E. du Pont de Nemours & Company, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 37)
- 10-CA-4312; A. D. Maxwell, d/b/a Southern Furniture Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 72, Folder 38)
  Cookeville, TN
- 10-CA-4311; Satchwell Electric Construction Company, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 39)
- 10-CA-4304; Radio Corporation of America Service Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 72, Folder 40)
- 10-CA-4299; Apex Linen Service, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 41)
- 10-CA-4306; Apex Linen Service, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 42)
- 10-CA-4305; O.B. Davis Construction Company, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 43)
- 6-CA-1695; Fisher Scientific Company, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- 6-CA-1740; Fields, Edward & Co., 1959 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- 6-CA-1741; Fields, Edward & Co., 1959 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- 6-CA-1746; Fields, Edward & Co., 1959 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- 6-CA-1744; Fields, Edward & Co., 1959 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- 6-CA-1745; Fields, Edward & Co., 1959 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- 6-CA-1737; Fields, Edward & Co., 1959 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- 6-CA-1742; Fields, Edward & Co., 1959 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- 6-CA-1753; True Temper Corporation, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  Union City, PA
- 6-CA-1752; True Temper Corporation, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- 6-CA-1118; Rockwell Manufacturing Company, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  DuBois, PA
- 6-CA-1618; Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- 6-CA-1494; Bingler Ford Sales, Inc., 1959 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  Johnstown, PA
- 6-CA-1263; Norbute Corporation, Metalab-Labcraft Division, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  Beverly, WV
- 6-CA-1262; Norbute Corporation, Metalab-Labcraft Division, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- 10-CA-4457; Georgia Rug Mill, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  Summerville, GA
- 10-CA-4462; Bowman Transportation, Inc., 1963 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-4462; Bowman Transportation, Inc., 1963 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-4540; Wate, Inc., 1963 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  Memphis, TN
- 10-CA-4640; Southern Electronic Company, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  Mosheim, TN
- 10-CA-4701; Diamond Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-4859; Burlington Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  Cleveland, TN
- 10-CA-4859; Burlington Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- 10-CA-4912; O. N. Jonas Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  Dalton, GA
- 10-CA-4915; East Tennessee Undergarment Company, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-4950; O. N. Jonas Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-4953; O. N. Jonas Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- 10-CA-4980; Nopco Chemical Company, Plant 13, Plastics Division, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- 10-CA-4981; Production Engineering Co., 1962 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  Austell, GA
- 10-CA-5014; Cincinnati Cordage and Paper Company, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- 10-CA-5029; Apex Linen Service of Columbus, Inc., 1963 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5037; Birmingham Fabricating Company, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5047; Krispy Kreme Doughnut Company, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-5058; Bagwell Electric Steel & Casting Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-5060; G & C Lingerie Company, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  Town Creek, Alabama
- 10-CA-5070; Krispy Kreme Doughnut Company, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- 10-CA-5082; Lowell Bleachery, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  South Experiment, GA
- 10-CA-5088; Nopco Chemical Company, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- 10-CA-5101; Hotel De Soto, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5103; White Castle Company Redstone Arsenal, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- 10-CA-5108; Dobbs Houses, Inc., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5109; Dr. Pepper Bottling Company of Chattanooga, Inc., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-5123; Brown Engineering Company, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-5125; U S Electronics Products, Inc., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  East Point, GA
- 10-CA-5148; Southern Oxygen Company, Division of Air Products & Chemical Co., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  Kingsport, TN
- 10-CA-5152; Howard Paper Company, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- 10-CA-5154; United States Pipe and Foundry Company, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- 10-CA-5155; Pinkerton National Detective Agency, Inc., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5156; Magnavox Furniture Company, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- 10-CA-5157; R. L. Ziegler, Inc., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  Tuscaloosa, Alabama
- 10-CA-5158; Bridgeport Brass Company, A Wholly Owned Subsidiary & Division of National Distillers, Inc., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  Moultrie, GA
- 10-CA-5161; Dixie Belle Mills, Inc., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  Calhoun, GA
- 10-CA-5171; Siskin Steel and Supply Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- 10-CA-5174; Koehring Company, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- 10-CA-5179; Allied Steel Products of Alabama, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5180; United States Plating & Bumper Service, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-5183; Dixie Belle Mills, Inc. Subsidiary of Bell Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-5184; John W. Bell, individually & as agent of R. L. Zeigler, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- 10-CA-5185; Southeastern Mills, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- 10-CA-5186; General Oil, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- 10-CA-5190; Burton Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  Jasper, Alabama
- 10-CA-5191; Fairway Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5192; Atlantic Thrift Company, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- 10-CA-5193; Brunswick Sports of Albany A Division of Brunswick Corp., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- 10-CA-5195; Kawneer Company, Division of American Climax, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- 10-CA-5199; Bellcraft, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- 10-CA-5208; Dixie Belle Mills, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- 10-CA-5201; Birmingham Fabricating Company, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- 10-CA-5206; Stamper Collins, d/b/a Wind Rock Coal & Coke Co., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  Oliver Springs, TN
- 10-CA-5207; Knox Glass, Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  Forrest Park, GA
- 10-CA-5204; Soil Pipe Division, United States Pipe & Foundry Co., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- United States Pipe and Foundry Company, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 18)
- Union Negotiating File, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Union Contract Proposal, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 20)
- U. S. Soil Pipe Division, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 21)
- 10-CA-5209; General Electric Company, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 22)
- 10-CA-5209; General Electric Company, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 23)
- 10-CA-5210; Newbury Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  Talladega, Alabama
- 10-CA-5211; Ryder Truck Rental, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 25)
- 10-CA-5212; Howard Paper Company, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 26)
- 10-CA-5213; Tom Huston Peanut Co., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 27)
- 10-CA-5214; Labor's Consumer Service Store Co., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  Alcoa, TN
- 10-CA-5215; G & C Lingerie Company, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 29)
- 10-CA-5217; Brown Engineering Company, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 30)
- 10-CA-5218; Ampex Corporation, Magnetic Tape Division, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  Opelika, Alabama
- 10-CA-5219; Standard Container Company, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  Homerville, GA
- 10-CA-5220; Birmingham Slag Division Vulcan Materials Company, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-5221; Dr. Pepper-Canada Dry Bottling Company, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  Chattanooga, Tennessee
- 10-CA-5222; Webb Decorating Co., 1963 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- 10-CA-5223; Aluminum Company of America, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- 10-CA-5224; Berkline Corporation, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- 10-CA-5225; Roberts & Son, its successor, Roberts & Son, Foster-Garrett and Hartzog, Inc., 1963 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5226; Lithonia Lighting Corp, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  Conyers, GA
- 10-CA-5227; Union Aluminum Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- 10-CA-5228; Apex Linen Service, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- 10-CA-5229; Jim Burke Buick Inc., 1963 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- 10-CA-5230; Brunswick-McGregor Sports, A Division of Brunswick Corp., 1963 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- 10-CA-5231; Okefenoke Cooperative, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  Nahunta, Ga
- 10-CA-5232; Camel Mfg. Co., 1963 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- 10-CA-5260; Western Electric Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5260; Western Electric Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-5295; Superior Trucking Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5296; U. S. Pipe & Foundry Company ( North Birmingham Plant ), 1963 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-5297; Cosmos Tablet Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-5299; Pennsalt Chemicals Corporation, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  Hapeville, GA
- 10-CA-5302; Vulcan Materials, Company, Birming-Slag Division for its Vulcan Signs & Stampings Plant, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- 10-CA-5304; Grundy Mining Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  Tracy City, TN
- 10-CA-5305; Tennessee Consolidated Coal Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- 10-CA-5306; Dobbs Houses, Inc., 1963 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5307; Pacal Corp., 1963 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  Jessup, GA
- 10-CA-5308; New King Mountain Coal Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- 10-CA-5309; King Jellico Coal Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- 10-CA-5310; K & S Coal and Clay Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- 10-CA-5311; Production Engineering Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- 10-CA-5312; Georgia-Florida-Alabama Transportation Co., 1963 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- 10-CA-5314; Southern Furniture Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- 10-CA-5315; Jim Burke Buick, Inc., 1963 (Box 82, Folder 16)
- 10-CA-5316; Brock Candy Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 17)
- 10-CA-5317; Roxbury Carpet Co., 1963 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- 10-CA-5318; C & H Tufting Corporation, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- 10-CA-5319; United States Steel Corporation, Tennessee Coal & iron Division, Ensley Steel Works, Utilities Department, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  Fairfield, Alabama
- 10-CA-5320; Levi Strauss Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 21)
- 10-CA-5261; Cullom and Ghertner Company, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5262; A. C. Samford Overseas, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-5263; South Way Discount Center, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-5264; Georgia Highway Express, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- 10-CA-5265; Crown Cork & Seal Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- 10-CA-5266; Cullman Products Corp., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- 10-CA-5267; Extron Plastic, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- 10-CA-5268; Vinylex Corporation, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5269; Production Engineering Company, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- 10-CA-5270; Dobbs Houses, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- 10-CA-5271; Holiday Inn of Atlanta-Northwest, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- 10-CA-5272; Tennessee Stove Workers, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- 10-CA-5273; Delta Tank Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- 10-CA-5274; Camel Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- 10-CA-5275; C & H Tufting Corp., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- 10-CA-5277; Woodcraft Corporation, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  York, Alabama
- 10-CA-5278; Chattanooga Boiler and Tank Company, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- 10-CA-5279; Apex Linen Service of Columbus, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 18)
- 10-CA-5280; Crown Cork & Seal Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 19)
- 10-CA-5281; Scholle Atlanta Corporation, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  College Park, GA
- 10-CA-5282; Kroger Company, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 21)
- 10-CA-5283; A. C. Samford Overseas, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 22)
- 10-CA-5284; Allied Steel Products Corp. of Alabama, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 23)
- 10-CA-5285; United States Steel Corporation, Tennessee Coal & Iron Division, Fairfield Steel Mill Motor Transportation Division, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 24)
- 10-CA-5286; The Woodcraft Corporation, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 25)
- 10-CA-5287; Rhonda Lee, Inc. et al, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 26)
- 10-CA-5288; Lanier Uniform Rental Service, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 27)
- 10-CA-5289; Floors, Inc., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 28)
- 10-CA-5290; Arthur G. McKee & Company, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  Charleston, TN
- 10-CA-5291; Girdler Corp., 1963 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  Louisville, KY
- 10-CA-5292; Sweetwater Rug Company, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  Ringgold, GA
- 10-CA-5293; Cabin Craft, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 32)
- 10-CA-5322; Miller's Department Store, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5323; Atlanta Driveway Co., Inc. Keheley Construction, Inc. and Central Paving, Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-5324; Georgia Highway Express, Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-5325; Lowe Furniture Corporation, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- 10-CA-5326; Dance Freight Lines, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- 10-CA-5327; Jim Burke Buick, Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- 10-CA-5328; Tennessee Electro - Minerals Corporation, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  Greeneville, TN
- 10-CA-5329; G & C Lingerie Company, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5331; Attalla Pipe & Foundry Co., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  Attalla, Alabama
- 10-CA-5332; Thompson Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  Algood, TN
- 10-CA-5333; Grundy Mining Company, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- 10-CA-5334; Hurd Lock & Manufacturing Co., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- 10-CA-5335; Georgia Shoe Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  Baxter, TN
- 10-CA-5336; King - Jellico Coal Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- 10-CA-5337; Rohm & Haas Company, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- 10-CA-5338; Brimstone Railroad, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  New River, TN
- 10-CA-5339; Terminal Transport Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- 10-CA-5340; Arthur G. McKee & Co., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- 10-CA-5342; The Alabama Limestone Division of Georgia Marble Company, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  Russellville, Alabama
- 10-CA-5343; Production Engineering Company, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  Austell, Georgia
- 10-CA-5344; Holiday Inn of Atlanta - Northwest, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- 10-CA-5345; Ampex Corporation, Magnetic Tape Division, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- 10-CA-5346; Valley Steel, Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  Fort Payne, Alabama
- 10-CA-5347; Bimporad Carpet Mills Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  Ft. Oglethorpe, GA
- 10-CA-5348; E. T. Barwick Carpet Mills Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  Lafayette, GA
- 10-CA-5349; Mar-Jac Poultry Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  Gainesville, GA
- 10-CA-5350; Gulf Mart Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 27)
- 10-CA-5351; Thompson Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 28)
- 10-CA-5352; Georgia Highway Express, Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 29)
- 10-CA-5353; United States Steel Corporation, Tennessee Coal & Iron Division, Rail Transportation Works, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 30)
- 10-CA-5355; Thompson Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 31)
- 10-CA-5358; J. P. Stevens & Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 32)
- 10-CA-5359; Gaby Hosiery Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 84, Folder 33)
  Dandridge, TN
- 10-CA-5360; Knox-Concrete Products Company, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 34)
- 10-CA-5361; Terminal Transport Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5362; Southern Furniture Manufacturing Co., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-5363; Sid E. Williams and Nell Williams, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  Powder Springs, GA
- 10-CA-5364; Central Alabama Electric Cooperative, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  Prattville, Alabama
- 10-CA-5365; Fiber Conversion Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- 10-CA-5366; Georgia Shoe Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- 10-CA-5368; Grundy Mining Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- 10-CA-5369; Tennessee Consolidated Coal Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5370; Tennessee Products and Chemical Corporation, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  Whitwell, TN
- 10-CA-5371; Chattanooga Royal Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- 10-CA-5372; M & S Steel Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- 10-CA-5373; Valley Steel, Inc., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- 10-CA-5374; Attalla Pipe & Foundry Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- 10-CA-5376; Southern Furniture Mfg. Co., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- 10-CA-5377; Pascal Corp., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- 10-CA-5381; J. P. Stevens Company, Exposition Plant, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- 10-CA-5382; Fork Mining Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  Devonia, TN
- 10-CA-5385; Wall Tube and Metal Products Co., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- 10-CA-5384; Georgia Shoe Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- 10-CA-5386; J. T. Schrimsher Construction Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- 10-CA-5387; Jefferson City Cabinet Co., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  Jefferson City, TN
- 10-CA-5388; Alabama Marble - Division of Georgia Marble Co., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  Sylacauga, Alabama
- 10-CA-5389; Dixie-Ohio Express, Inc., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 23)
- 10-CA-5390; United States Steel Corporation, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 24)
- 10-CA-5391; Fork Mountain Mining Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 25)
- 10-CA-5392; Fork Mountain Mining Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 26)
- 10-CA-5393; Birmingham Fabricating Company, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 27)
- 10-CA-5394; Gulf Atlantic Warehouse Co., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 28)
- 10-CA-5396; Foremost Processing Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 29)
- 10-CA-5397; Loew's Grand Theatre, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 30)
- 10-CA-5398; Loew's Grand Theatre, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 31)
- 10-CA-5399; Fulton Cotton Mills, Division of Fulton Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 85, Folder 32)
- 10-CA-5400; Planet Southern Corp., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5401; W. C. Caye Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- 10-CA-5403; Tennessee Stove Works, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-5404; Tom Huston Peanut Co., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- 10-CA-5406; Claussen Concrete Products, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  Augusta, GA
- 10-CA-5407; Bell-House Aluminum Windows, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  Stone Mountain, GA
- 10-CA-5409; Birmingham Fabricating Company, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- 10-CA-5410; Haralson Metals, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  Breman, GA
- 10-CA-5411; General Steel Tank Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- 10-CA-5413; Boss Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  Oneida, TN
- 10-CA-5414; Attalla Pipe & Foundry Company, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- 10-CA-5415; The White Stores, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- 10-CA-5417; Marx Brothers Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- 10-CA-5418; Atlantic Steel Company, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- 10-CA-5419; Knox Glass, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  Forest Park, GA
- 10-CA-5421; East Tennessee Undergarment Co., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 17)
- 10-CA-5422; Terminal Transport Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- 10-CA-5424; Wate, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 19)
- 10-CA-5425; Sheffield Southern Steel Products, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 20)
- 10-CA-5426; Fiber Conversion Company, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 21)
- 10-CA-5427; Southern Furn. Mfg. Co., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 22)
- 10-CA-5430; Metals Engineering Corporation, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 23)
- 10-CA-5432; Aunt Fanny's Baking Company, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 24)
- 10-CA-5433; Elliott Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 25)
- 10-CA-5434; D/B/A Rittenbaum Brothers, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 26)
- 10-CA-5435; Breeding Insulation Company, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 27)
- 10-CA-5436; Dobbs House, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 28)
- 10-CA-5437; Lamar Electric Membership Corporation, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  Barnesville, GA
- 10-CA-5438; Wall Tube and Metal Products Co., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 30)
- 10-CA-5439; Potter and Rayfield, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 31)
- 10-CA-5440; Great Dane Trailers, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 32)
- 10-CA-5441; Federal Services, Inc., 1963 (Box 86, Folder 33)
- 10-CA-5442; Sweetwater Rug Corporation, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 34)
- 10-CA-5444; The Alabama Limestone Division of Georgia Marble Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- 10-CA-5445; Tennessee Products & Chemical Corp., Roane Electric Furnace Division, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  Rockwood, TN
- 10-CA-5446; United States Steel Corporation, Tennessee Coal & Iron Division, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-5447; The Cotton Producers Association d/b/a Gold-Kist Poultry Growers, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- 10-CA-5448; Schnider Egg Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- 10-CA-5449; Knox Manufacturing Corporation, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- 10-CA-5450; Atlantic Mills Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- 10-CA-5451; Harry Rittenbaum, Louie Rittenbaum Mary Feen Rittenbaum, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- 10-CA-5452; Larkwood Farms, a division of Georgia Broilers Corp., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  Guntersville, Alabama
- 10-CA-5453; Refrigerated Transport Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- 10-CA-5454; Empire Coke Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- 10-CA-5455; Bowser Briggs Filtration Division, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- 10-CA-5456; Century Electric Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  McMinnville, TN
- 10-CA-5457; National Business Forms, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- 10-CA-5458; Kingsport Press, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- 10-CA-5459; The Jeffrey Mfg. Co., Morristown Division, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- 10-CA-5460; d/b/a Schneider Egg Co. Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 17)
- 10-CA-5461; Dixie Portland Flour Mill, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 18)
- 10-CA-5462; General Steel Tank Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 19)
- 10-CA-5463; Claussen Concrete Products Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 20)
- 10-CA-5464; Gordon Mills, Inc., Forrest Mills Div., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 21)
- 10-CA-5465; H. K. Porter Company, Inc. Refractories Division, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 22)
- 10-CA-5466; Jack Cole Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 23)
- 10-CA-5467; Jack Cole Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 24)
- 10-CA-5468; National Cabinet Corporation, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  Springville, Alabama
- 10-CA-5468; National Cabinet Corporation, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 26)
- 10-CA-5469; National Cabinet Corporation, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 27)
- 10-CA-5470; Ryder Truck Lines, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 28)
- 10-CA-5471; Waters Enterprises, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 29)
- 10-CA-5472; Century Electric Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 30)
- 10-CA-5473; Pullman-Standard, a Division of Pullman, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 31)
- 10-CA-5474; The Advance Specialty Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 32)
- 10-CA-5475; The Advance Specialty Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 33)
- 10-CA-5478; East Tennessee Packing Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 34)
- 10-CA-5479; G. H. Wickham Company, Stardust Cruiser Mfg. Company and James E. Chambers Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 35)
- 10-CA-5485; Cullom and Ghertner Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 36)
- 10-CA-5486; Boss Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 37)
- 10-CA-5480; United Motor Freight Terminal, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 38)
- 10-CA-5481; W. R. Grace and Company, Davison Chemical Division, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 39)
- 10-CA-5483; United States Steel Corporation, Tennessee Coal & Iron Division, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 40)
- 10-CA-5484; Lamar Electric Membership Corporation, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 41)
- 10-CA-5487; Allied Steel Products Corp. of Alabama, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 42)
- 10-CA-5488; Canton Cotton Mills, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 43)
- 10-CA-5490; Pullman-Standard A Division of Pullman, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 44)
- 10-CA-5491; M & S Steel Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 45)
- 10-CA-5492; Reynolds Metals Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 46)
- 10-CA-5493; Best Iron Works, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 47)
- 10-CA-5494; National Cabinet Corporation, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 48)
- 10-CA-5495; Colonial Food Stores, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 49)
- 10-CA-5497; Superior Trucking Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 50)
- 10-CA-5498; The Alabama Limestone, Division of Georgia Marble Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 51)
- 10-CA-5502; The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 87, Folder 52)
- 10-CA-5505; Boss Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 53)
- 10-CA-5508; National Cabinet Corporation, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 54)